hoosiertimes.com 2018-01-24

# Privacy Policy - Schurz Communications Inc.

**PRIVACY POLICY**

_Last Modified 12/12/2014_

Schurz Communications Inc. and the companies identified at [http://www.schurz.com/properties](http://www.schurz.com/properties/) (each, a “Company”) strive to offer visitors to its websites identified at [http://www.schurz.com/properties](http://www.schurz.com/properties/) (each, a “Site”) the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. In order to do so, we may obtain certain personal information from you. The purpose of this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you when you visit the Site, how we may use that information, and the choices you have regarding our use of that information. This Privacy Policy supplements and is incorporated as a part of Company’s Terms of Use, which may be available at <http://www.schurz.com/about/terms-of-use/>. Throughout this Privacy Policy, “we,” “us,” or “our” refers to Company, and “you” or “your” refers to the person or entity who accesses or uses this Site or its content (the “User”).

**RIGHT TO CHANGE POLICY**

Company reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to alter this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice to any User, including to comply with privacy laws, regulations and/or our own or industry standards or for other reasons as we deem necessary. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy each time you visit our Site. Your use of our Site at any time, including after any change to this Privacy Policy, indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, and any change made to this Privacy Policy or such Terms of Use.

**COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION FROM USERS**

We collect information on our Users in various ways, including by your voluntary submissions, through surveys, contests, sweepstakes and other promotions and through “cookies” and other tracking technology (as explained in more detail below). The information we collect is used in a variety of ways including, but not limited to: fulfilling and providing services requested by you; improving the Site and our services; collecting information about Users and their use of the Site; notifying you about updates to the Site and our services; and/or informing about products, services and promotions in which you may have interest. With your authorization or as otherwise permitted under this Privacy Policy, we may also share the information you provide with third parties.

**PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

Personally Identifiable Information refers to information that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name, phone number, e-mail, postal address or credit card information, and possibly information relating to certain support or customer service issues (“Personally Identifiable Information”).

You generally do not need to provide us with Personally Identifiable Information to use this Site or to obtain information from most of the features on the Site.

In some cases, however, you may be asked to provide Personally Identifiable Information in order to access certain pages of this Site, to use or subscribe to certain online services on this Site or other products or to allow us to provide you with certain personalized or enhanced services that you have requested. How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. As noted, you can visit many pages on our Site without providing any Personally Identifiable Information. Other pages may prompt you to provide Personally Identifiable Information.

If you do not wish to provide us with Personally Identifiable Information, you can decide not to use such services or access such pages on the Site.

Please remember that if you post Personally Identifiable Information in any public areas of the Site, such information may be collected and used by other Users over whom Company has no control. Company is not responsible for any use made by third parties of any information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of the Site.

**AGGREGATE INFORMATION**

From time to time, we may collect general, non-personal, statistical information about the use of the Site, such as how many visitors visit a specific page on the Site, how long they stay on that page, and which hyperlinks, if any, they click on. We collect aggregate information through the use of technologies such as cookies or other tracking technologies. This information represents a generic overview of our Users’ collective viewing habits and allows us and other third parties to modify information, promotions, offers and/or discounts on products and services based on user traffic and behavior. Please be assured that this aggregate data will in no way personally identify you or any other visitors of the Site.

We collect aggregate information: to enhance the Site for visitors; to determine which areas of the Site are most popular; to optimize third-party offers of products and/or services; to analyze the use of the Site and to disclose the results to our partners, service providers, advertisers, existing or potential business partners, or other third parties to enable the provision of targeted or interest-based information, promotions, offers and/or discounts on products and services; and/or in response to a government request.

**COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES**

Like most websites, this Site also may collect information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to Users. For example, Company may automatically collect non-personally identifiable information and data through the use of “cookies”. Cookies are small text files a website uses to recognize repeat Users, facilitate the User’s ongoing access to the website and facilitate the use of the website. Cookies also allow a website to track usage behavior and compile site usage information that will allow for the improvement of content and target advertising. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set your browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. However, please be aware that some features of our Site may not function or may be slower if you refuse cookies. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers or other third parties with links on the Site as described below. We do not control these cookies. The use of advertising cookies sent by third party ad servers is standard in the Internet industry.

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our Site is accessed. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web. Web servers, the computers that “serve up” web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We may link the information we record using tracking technologies to Personally Identifiable Information we collect at the Site for our own and our marketing partners’ marketing and advertising purposes. In addition, we reserve the right to use IP addresses and other tracking technologies to identify a visitor when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use, to protect our Site, our customers or others, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

The Site may also use technology called “tracer tags”. These may also be referred to as “Clear GIFs” or “Web Beacons”. This technology allows us to understand which pages you visit on the Site. These tracer tags are used to help us optimize and tailor our Site for you and other Users of our Site.

This Site may also use certain web analytics services provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze information about the Users of this Site and how Users use the Site. Using Google Analytics, this Site may collect data about you and your use of the Site via Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers, in addition to data collected through standard Google Analytics implementation. This data may include demographic, interest-based, and other information about you. The Google Analytics and related services utilized by this Site may include: Google Analytics Advertising Features, Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Platform integrations, Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, and similar services offered by Google and its partners (the “Google Services”). By using this Site, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google and Google’s partners consistent with their general practices and practices in relation to the Google Services.

Information generated by cookies about your use of this Site (including your IP address) may be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers. Google may use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of this Site, compiling reports on Site activity for Site operators and providing other services relating to Site activity and usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf.

You may be able to opt-out of the Google Services through Google Analytics’ available opt-outs for the web (which may be available at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>), through Ads Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or other available means, including the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) consumer opt-out, which may be available at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your particular browser. Please note, however, that if you disable cookies or opt-out of certain services, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this Site.

We may also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Site or perform remarketing services. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about you and your visits to this Site and other websites in order to provide interest-based advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. More information about interest-based advertising and similar practices may be available at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>.

**DISCLOSURES AND TRANSFERS OF INFORMATION**

We do not disclose Personally Identifiable Information about you to third-parties for their independent use unless:

  1. You have requested or authorized us to provide such information, including, but not limited to, “opting-in” to a particular service, program or promotion;
  2. The disclosure is permitted by relevant law;
  3. The disclosure is reasonably related to the sale or other disposition of all or part of our business or assets;
  4. The Personally Identifiable Information to be disclosed is publicly available;
  5. The party to whom the disclosure is made controls, is controlled by, or is under common control with Company;
  6. The disclosure is to persons or entities for whom we are providing services, provided the disclosure is consistent with the purpose for which the personal information was obtained;
  7. We have your permission to make the disclosure;
  8. The disclosure is necessary for the purpose for which the Personally Identifiable Information was obtained;
  9. The disclosure is necessary to fulfill services requested by you;
  10. The disclosure is to financial service providers in order to fulfill and carry out the purchase and provision of goods and services requested by you;
  11. The Personally Identifiable Information to be disclosed is otherwise publicly available in accordance with the applicable law;
  12. The disclosure is reasonably related to the sale or other disposition of all or part of our business or assets;
  13. The disclosure is for our own marketing purposes, or, with your authorization, for the marketing purposes of third parties;
  14. The party to whom the disclosure is made controls, is controlled by, or is under common control with Company;
  15. The disclosure is in our sole discretion necessary for the establishment or maintenance of legal claims or legal compliance, to satisfy any law, regulation, subpoena or government request, or in connection with litigation;
  16. The disclosure is in our sole discretion about users who we believe are engaged in illegal activities or are otherwise in violation of our terms of service, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order; or

  * The disclosure is to outside businesses to perform certain services for us, such as maintaining our Site and Services, mailing lists, processing orders and delivering products and services, sending postal mail, processing claims for lost or stolen certificates, providing marketing assistance, and data analysis (“Administrative Service Providers”), including Administrative Service Providers outside the country or jurisdiction in which you reside.

**AS A SERVICE TO OTHERS**

We may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for their marketing and/or advertising purposes. If you no longer want us to share your information (as discussed below), we will cease sharing your information. However, except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not control the third parties with whom we share such information and you will need to further notify such third parties if you would like them to cease use of your information.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we reserve the right to send you certain non-promotional communications to fulfill pending or ongoing services requested by you, relating to the Site (such as service announcements), e-mail related to purchases you have made or information you have submitted, or similar administrative or transactional messages.

**OUR SERVICE PROVIDERS**

We may sometimes use other businesses to perform certain services for us, such as hosting or maintaining our Site, storing your information, processing orders or subscriptions, or providing marketing assistance and data analysis. We may provide Personally Identifiable Information to service providers when that information is necessary for them to complete a requested transaction or otherwise perform their duties. Company will take reasonable steps to ensure that these service providers are notified of their obligations to reasonably protect Personally Identifiable Information on Company’s behalf.

**BUSINESS TRANSFERS**

As we continue to develop our business, we may buy other businesses or their assets or sell some or all of our business assets. Personally Identifiable Information and other customer information is generally one of the business assets involved in such transactions. Thus, in the event that Company or all of its assets are acquired, such information may be one of the transferred assets.

**PROTECTION OF COMPANY AND OTHERS**

Company fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities, and may in its sole discretion disclose Personally Identifiable Information or other information to satisfy any law, regulation, subpoena, or government request or in connection with litigation. Company reserves the right to release Personally Identifiable Information or other information about Users who we believe are engaged in illegal activities or are otherwise in violation of our Terms of Use, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order, if we believe in our sole discretion that such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to comply with any laws, to operate the Site, or to protect the rights or property of Company, its affiliates, or any of their officers, directors, or employees, agents, third party content providers, suppliers, sponsors, or licensors. Company also reserves the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities we reasonably believe in our sole discretion to be unlawful.

**DATA SECURITY AND INTEGRITY**

We take reasonable precautions to protect the privacy, accuracy and reliability of any information you provide and to protect such information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. The Personally Identifiable Information you provide and we collect is stored within databases that we control directly or through our service providers. As we deem appropriate, we use security measures consistent with industry standards, such as firewalls and encryption technology, to protect your information. However, since no security system is impenetrable, we cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. As a result, you transmit any information to or from the Site at your own risk.

If you create an account on this Site, you may be asked to choose a password for your account, in which case your online account information shall be protected by your password. We recommend that you do not disclose your password to any other person. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and Site account and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or Site account. You can access and update information in your account profile at any time by logging in to the website with your login name and password. Once you have logged in, you can update certain of your information such as your name, e-mail, password, and/or change your address.

**ACCESSING AND DELETING PERSONALLY IDENITIFIABLE INFORMATION; OPT-OUT**

We welcome you to contact us regarding whether Company is keeping information about you, the information we may be keeping, how we may be using your information or sharing your information with others, to update or delete your information, or to opt-out of the collection and use of your information. If you have submitted Personally Identifiable Information through the Site and you would like access to such information, please send an e-mail to privacy@schurz.com. We will use reasonable efforts to supply you with this information and to correct any factual inaccuracies that you identify. Please also contact us at privacy@schurz.com if you do not want us to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties or you want us to delete your Personally Identifiable Information from our databases. Keep in mind, however, that there may be residual information within our databases, access logs and other records, which may or may not contain such information. The residual information will not be used for commercial purposes; however, we reserve the right, from time to time, to re-contact former Users of this Site.

**AFFILIATED SITES, LINKED SITES AND ADVERTISEMENTS**

Company expects its partners, advertisers and third-party affiliates to respect the privacy of our Users. However, third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our Site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our Site you may link to, or view as part of a Company page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, websites or advertisement features offered by other parties through the Site. Company is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. Should you choose to voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on our Site, such as completing an online form request or e-mail link, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Company and this Privacy Policy.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

We understand and share your concerns regarding your children’s access to Internet and the Internet’s access to your children. Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we do not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from children under 13 years of age. If we learn that Personally Identifiable Information of a child under the age of 13 has been submitted to us via the Site or appears on or within the Site, we will take all action necessary to comply with our responsibilities under applicable legal requirements, including deleting any such information.

**DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS**

We do not currently employ a process for automatically responding to “Do Not Track” (DNT) signals sent by web browsers, mobile devices, or other mechanisms that may provide consumers a choice regarding the collection of Personally Identifiable Information about an individual consumer’s online activities. As is commonly the case with many other websites, third parties (e.g., advertisers) may be able to collect Personally Identifiable Information about your online activities over time and across different websites or online services when you use the Site.

**APPLICABLE LAW**

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the State of Indiana, United States of America, without regard to conflicts of law principles. Any action relating to this Privacy Policy must be filed and maintained in a state or federal court located in St. Joseph County, Indiana, United States of America, and each User consents to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in such courts for such purpose.

**CONTACT**

All requests, questions, or concerns about your Personally Identifiable Information or this Privacy Policy should be directed to Schurz Communications Inc.’s Privacy Officer via the following contact information:

_Attn: Privacy Officer_

Schurz Communications Inc.

_1301 E. Douglas Road_

_Mishawaka, IN 46545_

_Phone: 574-287-1001_

_Fax: 574-247-7238_
